http://www.quizmasters.com.au/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This document sets forth the Privacy Policy for PT Entertainment for our PubTriv game app and our websites www.pubtriv.com.au and www.quizmasters.com.au.
The goal we have here at PT Entertainment with our products is to provide you with a variety of fun challenges through trivia. You privacy is very important to us. If you have any questions or concerns, don't hesitate to contact us here.
Your Information
Our free PubTriv app allows you to compete with other players within the venue of your choice, and with other players in venues throughout Australia. Our free QuizMasters trivia game is designed for competition between individuals in any location. In both cases, we require little personal information except what is needed to allow the game to operate and for you to be identified as a potential prize winner. That is a name, user (screen) name email address and phone number. As we collect no money, and prizes are collected by competition winners at their local venues, no further information is required.
We respect your privacy and will endeavour to ensure your privacy is maintained when providing information electronically. To avoid the risk of another person accessing your account, please don't share your password with others.
For each visitor to reach the site, we expressively collect the following non-personally identifiable information, including but not limited to browser type, version and language, operating system, pages viewed while browsing the Site, page access times and referring website address. This collected information is used solely internally for the purpose of gauging visitor traffic, trends and delivering personalized content to you while you are at this Site.
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will use for these new purposes only, data collected from the time of the policy change forward will adhere to our updated practices.
We will not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to any outside party personally identifiable information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.
We train our employees about the importance of confidentiality and maintaining the privacy and security of your information. Access to your Personal Information is restricted to employees who need it to provide benefits or services to you.
This online service is hosted in Australia in secure, accredited facility. To help protect the privacy of data and personal information we collect and hold, we maintain physical, technical and administrative safeguards. Our security technology is updated on an ongoing basis.
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these third-party sites.
Google Analytics
We may use Google Analytics to help analyse how you use our website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google will store this information. We will not (and will not allow any third party to) use Google Analytics to track or to collect any personal information of visitors to our website. We will not associate any data gathered from this website with any personal information from any source as part of our use of Google Analytics.
If you do not want your website visit data reported by Google Analytics, you can install the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. For more details on installing and uninstalling the add-on, please visit the Google Analytics opt-out page.
Changes
Pt Entertainment’s Privacy Policy is subject to change from time to time. The most up to date version will always be available on this site. Your use of this website after any changes constitutes your agreement with this policy.
Contact
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you can to contact us here.
Quiz Venues
Merewether Bowling Club
Thursday - 7.00pm
-
Vouchers and giveaways every week!
23 Caldwell St, Merewether, NSW 2291
Phone:
(02) 4963 1461
View Site
Pedens Hotel - Cessnock
Thursday - 7.00pm
-
Skins Jackpot increasing weekly / Plenty of prizes and giveaways / Meal & drink specials on the night / Great family entertainment.
196 Vincent Street Cessnock NSW 2325
Phone:
02 4990 1014
View Site
Edgeworth Tavern
Wednesday - 7.30pm
-
Skins Jackpot: $100 - Increasing weekly until won - Family friendly Trivia - Heaps of prizes and giveaways - Free to play - Meal specials every night in restaurant
Cnr Minmi Rd & Main Rd Edgeworth
Phone:
02 4958 1772
View Site
The Park - Maitland Park Bowling Club
Wednesday - 7.00pm
-
Skins Jackpot: $100 - Increasing weekly until won - Family friendly Trivia - Heaps of prizes and giveaways - $2 to play - All money going to Jackpot - Meal specials every night in restaurant
Elgin Street Maitland
Phone:
02 4933 6815
View Site
The Albion Hotel
Wednesday - 7.30 PM
-
Skins Jackpot: $100 - Increasing weekly until won - Family friendly Trivia - Heaps of prizes and giveaways - Free to play - Meal specials every night in restaurant
Hannell Street Wickham
Phone:
02 4962 2411
View Site
Telarah Bowling Club
Tuesday - 6.30 pm
-
Skins Jackpot: Increasing weekly until won - Family friendly Trivia - Heaps of prizes and giveaways - $2 to play
All money to Jackpot pool - Meal specials every night in restaurant
Clarke Street Telarah
Phone:
02 4932 8278
View Site
Jewells Tavern
Tuesday - 6.30 PM
-
Skins Jackpot: $100 - Increasing weekly until won - Family friendly Trivia - Heaps of prizes and giveaways - Free to play - Meal specials every night in restaurant
Ntaba Rd Jewells / Shopping Center
Phone:
02 4948 9100
View Site
Club Catalina
Wednesday - 6.30 pm
-
Skins Jackpot: $100 - Increasing weekly until won - Family friendly Trivia - Heaps of prizes and giveaways - Free to play - Meal specials every night in restaurant
Rathmines
Phone:
02 4975 1955
View Site
The Clarendon Hotel
Thursday - 8 PM
-
Cash Jackpot, increasing weekly! Cash and vouchers each night!
347 Hunter St, Newcastle NSW 2300
Phone:
(02) 4907 6700
View Site
Belmont Hotel
Tuesday - 7.00pm
-
Skins Jackpot: $100 - Increasing weekly until won - Family friendly Trivia - Heaps of prizes and giveaways - Free to play - Meal specials every night in restaurant
483 - 485 Pacific Hwy Belmont NSW 2280
Phone:
02 4945 0444
View Site
Family Hotel - 607 High Street Maitland (Opposite the hospital)
Wednesday - 6.30 pm
-
Skins Jackpot: $100 - Increasing weekly until won - Family friendly Trivia - Heaps of prizes and giveaways - Free to play - Watch for our Themed Trivia nights held monthly - See our Facebook Page for details - https://www.facebook.com/thefamilyhotelmaitla
607 High Street Maitland NSW 2320
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Skins Jackpot: Increasing weekly / Club Vouchers and Giveaways
801 Pacific Highway Marks Point NSW 2280
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
0249 540 766
View Site
Argenton Hotel
Wednesday - 7:00pm and Monthly Themed Trivias (Contact Venue for Schedule)
-
Hotel Vouchers, Cash Jackpot
515 Lake Rd, Argenton NSW 2284
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
0249 550 588
View Site
Sydney Junction (SJs)
Tuesday - 7:30 pm
-
Great Food, Cash Jackpot
8 Beaumont Street Hamilton NSW 2303
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
Phone:
(02) 4929 1627
View Site
Copyright 2020 QuizMasters. Hosted by oneandthree studio. | Privacy Policy
